KANG SEONG-MIN, 29 YEARS OLD
JULY 16TH, 2016
LEFT, RIGHT
KARAOKE
PART-TIMER WANTED
CHRISANN MOTEL
KOREAN FOR BEGINNERS
WITH NEWS ANCHOR KANG EUN-JEONG
THE LATE MATTHEW GREEN, REST IN PEACE
A-JI
SPEEDY AND SAFE WASTE DISPOSAL
CHRISANN MOTEL
LONG-TERM STAY WELCOME
WAITING FOR MY DAY TO SOAR
AT MY HOMETOWN HOUSE, 1988
EUN-JEONG AT AGE 16
SBC
KANG EUN-JEONG'S NEWS DAY
SEONG-MIN
SEONG-MIN IS LEAVING
WAITING FOR MY DAY TO SOAR
BY KANG EUN-JEONG
KOREAN FOR BEGINNERS
NOTHING BUT THE TRUTH
MEET WITH KANG EUN-JEONG
NOTHING BUT THE TRUTH EVEN TOMORROW
KANG EUN-JEONG'S BOOK-SIGNING EVENT
MATTHEW, BE HAPPY!
KANG EUN-JEONG
SEONG-MIN
HEAL ANIMAL MEDICAL CENTER
A-JI
THE TRAGEDY OF AN ADOPTEE, MATTHEW GREEN
GOD'S GIFT, ABANDONED TILL THE END
MADAM
FINALLY, IT'S TOMORROW! AT 11:00 P.M.
DRINKING YOGURT, CHOCOLATE MILK
PUNCH DRUNK
CHRONIC TRAUMATIC ENCEPHALOPATHY
Subtitle translation by: Jean S Kim